fancast.com 2011-12-09

# Comcast.net Privacy Policy

**Effective October 7, 2011[Learn More](http://customer.comcast.com/Pages/FAQListViewer.aspx?topic=Internet&folder=cdf13524-c22a-49b8-9128-6896a8719ad0)**

## Summary (Jump to Full Policy)

The Web Services Privacy Policy describes the information Comcast collects about you, how Comcast uses that information, and how Comcast protects your privacy when you use the Websites and the services and software we offer here: [www.comcast.net](http://www.comcast.net/), [customer.comcast.com](http://customer.comcast.com/), [www.tunerfish.com](http://www.tunerfish.com/), and [www.plaxo.com](http://www.plaxo.com/).

This summary gives you some key points from the Privacy Policy, but you should read the whole Privacy Policy to get a full understanding of our privacy practices.

Please note: the Privacy Policy _does not_ tell you what information we collect and how we use it when you use other Comcast services (Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand, Comcast Digital Voice, Comcast High Speed Internet, XFINITY TV, XFINITY Voice, or XFINITY Internet). These services have their own privacy policy, which we post at <http://www.comcast.com/customerprivacy/> and mail to subscribers.

All of our Websites set forth in this Privacy Policy post the TRUSTe Seal. This means that TRUSTe has reviewed the privacy practices on these Websites, and you can contact TRUSTe about a privacy concern if we don't resolve it to your satisfaction.

We want you to understand what kinds of information may be collected about your use of the Websites and Web Services, and what we might do with that information.

Comcast collects two types of information from people who use its Websites: (i) information that identifies a particular person using a Website, and (ii) information that provides facts about a person without identifying him or her. 

## Information that Identifies Someone

Information that identifies a particular person could be a name, address or Social Security number, for example. We will not share this information with an advertiser, and we will not share it with another Website or company, unless you tell us to (for example, if you want to post information from your Plaxo page on your Facebook page or you want to use Tunerfish to tell your Twitter network about a television show you are watching).

We also use this kind of identifying information to provide services to you. For example, we may use it to bill you for services, to check your credit, to confirm your identity when you login, or to communicate with you. Sometimes we use other companies to help us provide our services. We may share your information with these companies, but they are required to protect it and to use it only to provide services to you.

## Information that Does Not Identify a Specific Person

Information that _does not_ identify a person could be a non-personal record of online activity, or information you put in a profile - like your zip code, your age or your gender (when it's used without your name). We routinely collect this kind of information and use it to improve your experience, -for example, by showing you content and advertising that may be more relevant and interesting to someone like you. Sometimes we share this kind of non-personal information with other companies that help us deliver and improve our services.

## Your Information May be Shared Among Comcast Companies

The Web Services are provided by various companies that are part of Comcast. We may share your information among these Comcast companies so we can make it easier for you to use several Web Services seamlessly. Also, if you use the Web Services in connection with other Comcast services (for example, to set your DVR online to record a show on your television), we may need to share your information with the Comcast companies that offer those services, too.

## Disclosure of your Information 

We respect and protect your privacy, but it is possible that we may be required to provide information about you to a court or law enforcement agency. We will only disclose your information if we are legally required to do so—if we receive a valid subpoena, court order, or search warrant, for example.

## Your Choices

We want you to know how you can control the personal information that we may collect. When you use the Websites and Services that post the Privacy Policy, you are agreeing that the policy applies to you.

## Registering

You may choose not to register for any one of the Web Services (or for all of them) if you do not want to share information that identifies you when you use that Website.

If you do register, we will give you a chance to create a profile. We may use some of the information in that profile to choose the content and advertising we think you would like to see.

When you register, we may also send you email about other products and services. You may choose not to receive these messages. However, we will still send you email with information about the specific services you use.

## Plaxo and Tunerfish

Plaxo users have several choices about how to share information from their address books and calendars. Tunerfish users have several choices about how to share information about themselves and the television shows they watch. The Privacy Policy explains how you can make those choices.

## Advertising Networks

Advertising networks help us display ads to you. They may use cookies and other technology to identify your interests so they can give you more useful ads. In the Privacy Policy, we give you the links to the “opt-out” pages for the ad networks that we use. You can elect to tell them not to collect information from you.

## Blogs and Forums

If you choose to post information on blogs or forums on the Websites, it will not be private. Once the information is posted, other users may copy or store it.

## Transferring Information to Social Networking Sites and Services

You may choose to use social networking Websites to share information from your Comcast profile, or information about what you do when you use the Comcast Web Services. If we get instructions to send your information to one of these Websites, with your valid Comcast login information included, we will accept the instructions to transfer your information.

If Comcast's business changes—for example, if our company merges with another company or we sell one or more of the Comcast companies that provide the Web Services—we may give the new owners of the Web Services your information. If this happens, we will tell you. We will also let you know if the Privacy Policy changes for any other reason, so you can decide whether you want to continue using the Web Services.

1\. About the Privacy Policy and the Comcast Web Services

The Comcast family of companies respects your privacy. Within this Web Services Privacy Policy (" **Privacy Policy** ") the term " **Comcast** " or " **we** " will refer to Comcast Cable Communications Management, LLC, Comcast Interactive Media, LLC, and their respective subsidiaries and affiliates that own and operate Websites and Internet services on their behalf. The term " **you** " refers to you as a user of Comcast's Websites or Internet services described below. The term " **Personally Identifiable Information** " or " **PII** " refers to information that identifies a specific person, such as the person's name, address, social security number, financial account number, or phone number. The term " **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** " or " **non-PII** " refers to information that is demographic, aggregated, or does not otherwise identify a specific person, such as a person's age, gender, ZIP code, or other information when that information is not used with Personally Identifiable Information.

## What does this Privacy Policy cover? 

This Privacy Policy explains how Comcast will use the information that you provide when you use these Comcast-owned and operated Websites and services:

  1. the Websites [www.comcast.net](http://www.comcast.net/), [customer.comcast.com](http://customer.comcast.com/), [www.tunerfish.com](http://www.tunerfish.com/), and [www.plaxo.com](http://www.plaxo.com/) (the " **Comcast Sites** "); and 
  2. all software and services provided by Plaxo, including those services made available through its application programming interfaces (" **APIs** ") (collectively the " **Plaxo Service** "); and
  3. all other software and services provided by Tunerfish, including those services made available by Tunerfish through its APIs (collectively the " **Tunerfish Service** ", and collectively, (1), (2), and (3) the " **Comcast Web Services** "). 

## What is outside the scope of this Privacy Policy? 

This Privacy Policy **_does not apply_** to your use of any other products or services provided by Comcast such as Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand, Comcast Digital Voice, Comcast High Speed Internet, XFINITY TV, XFINITY Voice, or XFINITY Internet. If you subscribe to or use one or more of these services, you can see the privacy policy that applies to the residential versions of these services by visiting <http://www.comcast.com/customerprivacy/>.

This Privacy Policy also **_does not apply_** to Comcast's use of information provided by you when you sign up for or use the XFINITY TV Store (xfinitytvstore.comcast.net). Comcast's use of the information you provide through the XFINITY TV Store is described in the XFINITY TV Store Privacy Policy, available at <http://xfinitytvstore.comcast.net/PrivacyPolicy.aspx>.

Some of the Comcast Web Services contain links to other Websites, including Websites of third parties who are acting on our behalf as our agents, suppliers, or providers. These other Websites are not operated by Comcast and have their own privacy policies that we encourage you to read before you use them. Other sites that we link to may contain Comcast branding, but these non-Comcast Websites and resources are provided by companies or persons other than Comcast. Examples of these non-Comcast Websites include Websites where you are required to log-in using a username and password other than your username and password for the Comcast Web Services, such as the Jobs channel and the Dating channel on Comcast.net. This Privacy Policy **_does not apply_** to those non-Comcast sites. Those sites will have their own policies that we encourage you to read before you use them.

2\. Comcast is a Member of TRUSTe

Comcast has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and the practices set forth in it have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at CIM_privacy at Comcast dot com. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

TRUSTe does not review or certify the privacy practices related to any other Comcast Websites, software programs, products, or services including Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand, Comcast Digital Voice, Comcast High Speed Internet, XFINITY TV, XFINITY Voice, XFINITY Internet, or the XFINITY TV Store.

3\. Collection of Information 

## All Users

Comcast, or third parties acting on Comcast's behalf, routinely logs Non-Personally Identifiable Information that is automatically generated when all users visit or use the Comcast Sites, as a by-product of the user's activities (" **Web Log Data** "). This information includes, but is not limited to, Internet protocol (" **IP** ") header information that is automatically passed between a user's computer and the Comcast Sites, such as the computer's IP address, the browser being used at the time, and the URL of the webpage on the Comcast Sites that the browser requested. This information may also include details relating to the activities users perform within the Comcast Sites, such as what links they click on, in what order they access specific web pages within the Comcast Sites, and the search queries they perform on the Comcast Sites.

Some of the Comcast Web Services allow you to store certain details and preferences that help you personalize that Comcast Service (" **Preference Data** "). This Non-Personally Identifiable Information may include ZIP code, age, gender, favorite genre to watch on television, and preferred type of news. Comcast stores Preference Data in a cookie that it places on your computer. We do this so that you do not have to enter this data every time you return to the Comcast Sites. We may also use the Preference Data to deliver other personalized services and features of the Comcast Web Services.

## Registered Users

Comcast asks you to provide certain information when you initially register to use the Comcast Web Services and then afterwards may ask you to provide additional information when you use certain Comcast Web Services for the first time. In addition, Comcast also collects information about your use of the Comcast Web Services as a registered user. This table summarizes the different types of information that we may collect from you when you register for the Comcast Web Services and use the Comcast Web Services as a registered user.

Type/Name 

| 

When Collected

| 

Representative Examples  
  
---|---|---  
  
Registration Data

| 

When you create an account for the Comcast Web Services or subsequently modify your Registration Data

| 

First and last name, username, password, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, gender, and date of birth   
  
Profile Data

| 

The first time you access certain Comcast Web Services after you have created an account or subsequently modify your Profile Data

| 

Additional e-mail addresses, lists of people to connect with through certain Comcast Web Services, school affiliations, movie genre preferences, and notification preferences for products and services made available by Comcast  
  
Activity Data

| 

When you log-in to your account and use the Comcast Web Services

| 

Flagging or rating news articles, movies, television shows or other content, posting blog entries or comments, sharing URLs, and content and data feeds from non-Comcast social networks or services that you choose  
  
Collectively, your Registration Data, Profile Data, Activity Data, and any other generally available demographic data about you that Comcast gathers from other sources is referred to as " **Your Data**." Your Data does not include information that third parties may independently gather from other Websites about you using their own cookies, as further described in this Privacy Policy.

Most Comcast Sites have their own pages where you can manage certain portions of your Registration Data and Profile Data relevant to that specific Comcast Site. For your reference, those pages can be found here:

<http://xfinitytv.comcast.net/mytv/settings>

<http://www.plaxo.com/settings/account>

4\. Use of Information

Comcast uses Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data, including both Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information in both aggregated and individual forms, to provide the Comcast Web Services and support them. We may process and use this data for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy including, but not limited to:

  * Customize, measure, and improve the Comcast Web Services, and the content and advertising provided through them;
  * Enforce our Web Services Terms of Service and detect fraud and other illegal activities;
  * Bill and collect for any applicable fees or charges;
  * Let you know about new products or services from Comcast or other companies we work with as well as promotional offers, based on your preference settings;
  * Let you know about changes to the Comcast Web Services, the Web Services Terms of Service, this Privacy Policy, and other terms that apply to our services; and
  * Update any programs or other tools that we provide in conjunction with the Comcast Web Services.

Comcast may use Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data in these forms for internal business purposes, such as determining how much traffic certain portions of the Comcast Web Services receive, for license reporting and assessment of service levels, to better understand how the Comcast Web Services are used, to gauge traffic patterns and determine what types of content and services are most popular with users of the Comcast Web Services, or determining which search queries on certain Comcast Service are the most popular.

Comcast may also use Web Log Data, Preferences Data, and Your Data to customize the Comcast Sites and Services and make them more relevant to you. For example, Comcast may use such data to determine which news articles, movies, or television shows to recommend to you.

Comcast may use your Registration Data to verify that you are the person authorized to use the Comcast Web Services or to manage your account. Comcast may also use your Registration Data to determine whether your Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand subscription allows you to access premium content or services offered through some of the Comcast Sites. For example, Comcast may use this subscription information to permit you to access, via one or more of the Comcast Web Services, certain programming included in your Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand package or to recommend additional Comcast products and services that it thinks may be of interest to you.

5\. Sharing of Information

Comcast uses third parties to assist us in delivering parts of the Comcast Web Services to you. We may share portions of Your Data with these third parties to the extent necessary for them to provide these services. These companies are acting on Comcast's behalf and are required, by contract with Comcast, to keep this information confidential and are only authorized to use it for specific purposes. As described in more detail below, Comcast may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information elements of Your Data to third parties who deliver ads to you on Comcast's behalf. Comcast will not provide your Personally Identifiable Information to these advertisers unless you expressly authorize us to do so.

Comcast may also share Web Log Data and Preference Data, which do not contain Personally Identifiable Information, with third parties. For example, Comcast may share traffic data for one of the Comcast Sites with a third party that analyzes and publishes Website traffic surveys. Or, Comcast may share Web Log Data and Preference Data with one of the providers of movies on xfinitytv.comcast.net, so that Comcast and the provider can determine what additional movies that provider should show on xfinitytv.comcast.net.

Comcast may also share Web Log Data, Preference Data, and Your Data within its internal family of companies solely to provide you with the Comcast Web Services, other cross-platform services, and advertising it thinks may be of interest to you. For example, Comcast will share your Registration Data within its internal family of companies to provide you with online access to content from premium networks that are part of your Comcast Digital Cable with On Demand subscription if you have signed up for that service, and to make you aware of other Comcast products and services it thinks may be of interest to you. This sharing occurs when you sign up for and use these other services, and may be necessary for us to provide them. If you do not want Your Data shared with a specific service, then you may choose not to sign up for that service or stop using it at any time if you have already signed up for it.

You may authorize other Internet sites such as MySpace or Facebook to access and publish on their Websites some of Your Data, including your Activity Data. For example, you may enable a Facebook widget to access and publish to your Facebook page what shows you watch on xfinitytv.comcast.net. In addition, certain Comcast Web Services allow you to use your contact lists from Internet sites such as MySpace or Facebook to share portions of Your Data, including your Activity Data, with others. For example, www.tunerfish.com may allow you to "check-in" to your favorite television show on xfinitytv.comcast.net, and then let all of your Facebook friends know what you are watching. If you provide Comcast with your credentials for this kind of Internet service and use the features of the Comcast Service that share information across these Internet services, or, if one of these Internet service contacts Comcast using your Comcast Web Services credentials and asks to have access to certain portions of Your Data, Comcast will treat this as your authorization to share such portions of Your Data with that Internet service.

6\. Advertisements

Comcast, or advertising network providers acting at Comcast's request, may deliver advertisements to you through the Comcast Web Services, depending on whether you are a registered user or not, as described in more detail below.

## All Users

We, or our advertising providers, automatically deliver ads to all users of the Comcast Sites, whether they are registered or not, based on non-personal information including: (i) the IP address associated with your computer for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location; (ii) the type of web page that is being displayed, such as a news or sports page, for example; or (iii) the content on the page that is shown, such as a sports article about a certain team or a movie review for a particular movie. Because this advertising activity automatically applies to all users and it is purely contextual, this type of advertising delivery cannot be customized or controlled by individual users.

## Registered Users

If you are a registered user, Comcast may use Your Data, regardless of where we gathered such information, to determine what type of ad to display to you on the Comcast Sites. For example, Comcast may use portions of Your Data that it gathered on www.comcast.net to determine which ad to show you when you visit xfinitytv.comcast.net. In addition, Comcast may send certain demographic information, like ZIP code, age, and gender to its advertising network providers, so that the advertising you see is more relevant to you. These advertising network providers will only use such information to display an ad to you on the Comcast Sites. 

7\. Advertising Networks and Other Service Provider Networks 

The advertising companies who deliver ads for us on the Comcast Sites may use HTTP cookies and Flash cookies to uniquely distinguish your web browser and keep track of information relating to serving ads on your web browser, such as the type of ads shown and the web pages on which the ads appeared. In addition, the third parties that provide Web Log services for Comcast may use cookies to uniquely distinguish your web browser and to keep track of the Websites that your web browser visits across the service provider's network of Websites. For more information on controlling HTTP and Flash cookies, please visit our "Customer Control" FAQ, [here](http://customer.comcast.com/%28S%28shfddi55euzxgy55jkrbmi45%29%29/Pages/FaqDisplay.aspx?Guid=dfcbf43e-91b2-4444-a04d-8d7c68fcb356#custcontrol).

Some of these companies may combine information they collect from the Comcast Sites with other information they have independently collected relating to your web browser's activities across their network of Websites. These companies collect and use this information under their own privacy policies. More information about these companies, their privacy policies, and the opt-outs they offer can be found here:

### Ad Choices

8\. Communicating with You 

Comcast may use your Registration Data to send you a confirmation e-mail verifying the ownership of the e-mail addresses provided in your Registration Data and to send you service-related communications about the Comcast Web Services. In addition, Comcast may send you promotional or commercial e-mail relating to each Comcast Site for which you have activated your account as permitted by applicable law. You can opt-out from receiving such promotional or commercial e-mail by following the instructions contained in the e-mails or by going to:

<http://xfinity.comcast.net/subscribe/>

<http://www.plaxo.com/settings/email>

<http://www.comcast.com/preferences>

<http://www.tunerfish.com/settings>

and following the directions there. 

Non-members may elect to permanently opt-out from receiving invite requests from members to join Plaxo. When you register for permanent opt-out, you provide us with a validated e-mail address at which you no longer wish to receive Plaxo invite requests. Comcast may send you an opt-opt confirmation e-mail to the address you enter. If you are sent an opt-out confirmation e-mail, you must respond to that e-mail to complete the opt-out process. The opt-out is available here:

<http://www.plaxo.com/opt_out>

9\. Signing in Using Non-Comcast Credentials 

Comcast may allow you to access portions of the Comcast Web Services by signing in using your username or other identifier from another Internet service (" **Non-Comcast Username** "). Comcast will treat your Non-Comcast Username and any additional data that the relevant Internet service provides to Comcast about you as Your Data. 

10\. Participating in Blogs and Forums

If you post comments to any of the blogs, forums, or other editorial sections of the Comcast Web Services, any information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of the Comcast Web Services and any PII you post could be used to contact you. We are not responsible for PII you choose to submit through these features.

Children under the age of 13 should not post in any of the blogs, forums, or other editorial sections of the Comcast Web Services.

11\. Security

Comcast uses industry standard approaches to securely store, control access to, and make appropriate use of Your Data, and we require our contractors and other providers to do so as well. However, no security measure is completely effective and Comcast cannot guarantee the complete security of Your Data. If you don't want Comcast to know any particular information about you, you should not register to use the Comcast Web Services or include it in anything that you submit or post to Comcast, including posts on the Comcast Sites or e-mails to Comcast. More information on Internet security can be found here: <http://security.comcast.net/>. 

Comcast also takes additional steps to increase the security and reliability of customer communications. We do not read your outgoing or incoming e-mail, file attachments, video mail, private chat, or instant messages. However, we (along with our third party providers) use software and hardware tools to help prevent and block "spam" e-mails, viruses, spyware, and other harmful or unwanted communications and programs from bring sent and received over Comcast.net e-mail and the Comcast Sites. These tools may automatically scan your e-mails, video mails, instant messages, file attachments, and other files and communications in order to help us protect you and the Service against these harmful or unwanted communications and programs. You can learn more about Comcast's anti-spam approach at <http://help.comcast.net/content/faq/What-is-Comcast-doing-about-spam>.

As an additional security precaution, neither Comcast nor any of our authorized service providers will ask you for your Comcast password in an e-mail, over the telephone, or in an online support forum or chat area. **Do not give your Comcast password to anyone in an e-mail, over the telephone, or in an online support area**.

12\. Disclosures of Information

Comcast holds customer privacy in the highest regard and we make every reasonable effort to protect your privacy as described in this Privacy Policy. Nevertheless, we may be required by law to disclose Personally Identifiable Information or other information about you or other users of the Comcast Web Services. These disclosures may be made with or without your consent, and with or without notice, in compliance with the terms of a subpoena, court order, search warrant, or other valid legal process. We may also disclose information about you or users of the Comcast Web Services when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent financial loss, address suspected illegal activity, protect our rights or property, or prevent imminent physical harm.

13\. Special Note About Children

Comcast does not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from anyone under the age of 13 without first obtaining parental consent. For those portions of the Comcast Web Services that do collect information from children under the age of 13 after obtaining parental consent, Comcast or its contractors will provide a special notice or other information describing any additional privacy protections that may apply. Children should always get permission from a parent or legal guardian before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers) over the Internet, to Comcast or to anyone else. 

14\. Your California Privacy Rights

California law permits its residents to request and receive information about a business' disclosure of certain categories of PII to other companies for their use for direct marketing. If you are a California resident and a user of any of the Comcast Web Services, you can request a copy of this information from Comcast Interactive Media, LLC by sending e-mail to CIM_Privacy at Comcast dot com or a letter to Comcast Interactive Media, LLC, Attn: California Direct Marketing Information, One Comcast Center, Philadelphia, PA 19103. Please include your name and e-mail address in e-mail requests, and your name and postal address in mail requests.

15\. Change of Ownership or Other Business Transaction

In the event Comcast enters into a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, or the sale of all or part of its assets (a " **Business Transition** "), Your Data (including PII and non-PII associated with the Comcast Web Services) will likely be part of the assets transferred. 

In this event, we will notify you of any Business Transition. We will also notify you of any subsequent material changes to this Privacy Policy as a result of a Business Transaction and give you the opportunity to opt-out for information that we have collected before, or may collect after, a new Privacy Policy containing material changes takes effect.

16\. Plaxo

The following terms in this section apply only to your use of the Plaxo Service and www.plaxo.com (collectively the " **Plaxo Offerings** "). 

Plaxo is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S.Department of Commerce and the European Union. Plaxo has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Website.

Comcast uses Your Data to enable you to use the Plaxo Offerings as follows. 

  * Registration Data and Profile Data. The name you put in your Registration Data and the photo (if you have uploaded one) in your Profile Data will be displayed to members; and to non-members who use the Plaxo Service if you choose to make the data publicly accessible. This is primarily so your friends, family or business colleagues can find you and connect with you. All users can control whether or not their names are listed in the Plaxo people search listings. You also control how all other information in your Registration Data and Profile Data is shared with others through your Plaxo privacy settings (for example, friends, family, business) located at <http://www.plaxo.com/settings/account>. You control whether or not you have a public profile. If you have a public profile you choose which information from your Registration Data and Profile Data is part of your public profile. Public profiles are viewable by any member or non-member who uses the Plaxo Service.
  * Activity Data. You control with whom your Activity Data is shared. Once you share data with someone, however, you cannot control what those recipients do with your data.

A special note about the contacts stored in your Plaxo address book and Plaxo's Personal Assistant:

Plaxo provides its members with updated contact information for the people they already have in their address books. Plaxo uses publicly available contact information corresponding to the contacts in a Plaxo member's address book, and suggests updates for that contact information to the Plaxo member. To help Plaxo determine whether a piece of publicly available contact information is accurate, Plaxo looks at how frequently that public information appears in the aggregation of all address book data stored in the Plaxo system. Plaxo members who do not want their address book data used in this aggregation process can easily remove their address book data from the Plaxo Offerings. Before removing the data, Plaxo members can export it to another online address book provider. Learn more about [exporting your address book](http://help.plaxo.com/article.asp?article=1490&p=16) and [deleting your account](http://help.plaxo.com/article.asp?article=1218&p=16).

Anyone, whether a Plaxo member or not, can prevent Plaxo from suggesting updates to their contact info as it appears in a Plaxo member's address book by [opting out](http://www.plaxo.com/optOut).

17\. Tunerfish

The following terms in this section apply only to your use of the Tunerfish Service and www.tunerfish.com (collectively the " **Tunerfish Offerings** ").

Comcast uses Your Data to enable you to use the Tunerfish Offerings as follows. 

  * Registration Data and Profile Data. Some of your Registration Data and Profile Data, for example your name, bio, and photo, is publicly available through the Tunerfish Offerings. You can control the contents of these fields, but any content you put in these fields will be viewable by anyone who visits the Tunerfish Website or uses the Tunerfish Offerings.
  * Activity Data. By default, your Activity Data is viewable by anyone who visits the Tunerfish Website or uses the Tunerfish Offerings. You may make your Activity Data more private by changing your Tunerfish privacy settings at <http://www.tunerfish.com/settings>. Once you share your Activity Data with someone, you cannot control what that person does with your data. You may choose to share your Activity Data with third parties (e.g., Facebook, Twitter) (" **Third Party Sites** "). If you choose to share your Activity Data with any Third Party Sites, they may use that data as described in their own privacy policies and other applicable terms and conditions.

18\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Comcast reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time consistent with applicable privacy laws. When we do change it, we will make a copy of the updated Privacy Policy available to you before it takes effect. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will also notify you by e-mail, direct mail, or other reasonable methods that we select. In the event of material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will give you the opportunity to opt-out for information that we have collected before, or may collect after, a new Privacy Policy containing material changes takes effect.

You understand and agree that if you use the Comcast Web Services after the effective date of the updated Privacy Policy, Comcast will consider your use as acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy.

19\. International Visitors 

Our computer systems are currently based in the United States, so your PII will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may be different than other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an online account to use the Comcast Sites as a visitor from outside the United States, you will have agreed to the terms of the Privacy Policy and our Web Services Terms of Service and you will have consented to the transfer to and processing of all such information in the United States, which many not offer an equivalent level of protection of that in the European Union or certain other countries. 

20\. Contacting Comcast & Customer Support

You can direct questions regarding this Privacy Policy to Comcast by e-mailing us at CIM_privacy at Comcast dot com. You can also send a letter by mail to Comcast Interactive Media, LLC, Attn: Privacy Policy Questions, One Comcast Center, Philadelphia, PA 19103 USA.

You can find customer support and help information at <http://customer.comcast.com/Pages/Help.aspx>. Some online support areas and tools may ask you to provide information to Comcast to help us address your questions or problems. We may also make software tools available to help configure your computer's or network's settings, or collect information from your computer or network to help us provide support to you. If you choose to provide this information to Comcast or use these tools, we will use the information only for customer support purposes.

Revised and Effective: October 7, 2011
